<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ezekiel Haggart</title>
    <link>http://ezekiel.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ezekiel Haggart</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ezekiel.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project TARR</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/presentation/tarr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/presentation/tarr/</guid>
      <description>All figures are made up for illustrative purposes
A project I am proud of is rolling out a strategy to send fraud rejected traffic to 3DS unlocking 40+ million in benefit from otherwise declined good customers. Why am I proud of this, well it worked. Until it didn&amp;rsquo;t. Righting the ship was a challenge and ultimately makes the project more interesting.
Agenda So what are we going to talk about today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph networks and fraud</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/post/2021-04-26-graph-networks-and-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/post/2021-04-26-graph-networks-and-fraud/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>90 day plan</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/presentation/90-day-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/presentation/90-day-plan/</guid>
      <description>In creating my 90 day plan I leant on the overall mission of the data function at Transpower which can be summarised succinctly as &amp;ldquo;Enhancing decision making&amp;rdquo;. Then taking assumptions from previous conversations, I feel I have a solid understanding of where the organisation wants to be in 3 years time.
  Self servicing
  Automated tests, alerting, pipelines and deployments
  Predictive analytics
  Data as a service</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using R and GIT to host a free pesonal site</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/post/using-r-and-git-to-host-a-pesonal-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/post/using-r-and-git-to-host-a-pesonal-site/</guid>
      <description>When I can I try to use R so when looking to put a personal site together a few years back I thought it was a good time to explore the blogdown package. Using this I was able to build and maintain the site using mostly R, GIT and a good grasp of how to google css/html.
I thought I would detail a step by step how to follow this to create a barebones copy and how to host it (for free) on GITHUB&amp;rsquo;s pages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using BTC exchange to find currency arbitrage</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/post/using-btc-exchange-to-find-currency-arbitrage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/post/using-btc-exchange-to-find-currency-arbitrage/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin cryptocurrency is treated as both a currency and more and more an asset that is exchanged across multiple FX across the globe. This presents an interesting question does the market balance the FX across currencies in real time? If not there would be room for arbitrage and a real ability to make money transferring between currencies using BTC markets.
This quick analysis will look to see if it is theoretically possible to make money changing NZD for BTC then to GBP and back to NZD via a BTC exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bars per capita in NZ</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/post/looking-at-the-density-of-bars-accross-nz-lla-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/post/looking-at-the-density-of-bars-accross-nz-lla-s/</guid>
      <description>In New Zealand to distribute alcohol you need to apply to your regional Liqour Licence Authority (LLA) for a permit. The NZ Justice Department produces a list of all liqour licences distributed in a single year.
I made this shiny app using a data set from NZ Justice Department and a shapefile/population statistics from Statistics to show for each LLA how many persons per bar, club or liqour retailer. This can be understood as bars per capita for NZ grouped by LLA&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christchurch Election</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/post/christchurch-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/post/christchurch-election/</guid>
      <description>Christchurch is New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s second largest city and in the 2017 election cycle it was a key prize for any of the political parties. I produced a series of interactive graphics to examine the outcome of Christchurch&amp;rsquo;s current and past three election cycles. The analysis was built using data sourced from data.govt.nz and elections.org.nz. The boundries of some of the Christchurch electorates reach beyond the city limits but for the sake of this assessment the electorates were kept as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezekiel Haggart</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Zeke I am from New Zealand based in Amsterdam. I am interested in data, history, politics and the environment. Totally an R and Shiny nerd but spend most of my time working in Python.
Mostly this site is an excuse to write some Shiny apps and as a place potential recruiters can see that I have enough ability to run blogdown::build_site() I am excited to learn how I can help with charitable or open source projects especially focused on sustainability and environmental causes, please reach out to me on linkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://ezekiel.nz/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ezekiel.nz/search/</guid>
      <description>search</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
